advancedpokertraining.com 2011-11-29

# Privacy Policy - Advanced Poker Training

We Value Your Privacy 

Simply put, our privacy policy is as follows: 

**"We value your privacy and will NEVER sell your personal information to ANYONE for ANY REASON. We only collect the information we need to provide you with our product, and we will guard your personal information with utmost security. Your personal information will only be stored on SSL secured servers and we will never store your personal information in hard copy form.** "

Specifically:

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically collects **no** information regarding your domain or e-mail address, except to prevent the abuse of our site or sharing of memberships.

We collect aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to restore our customer's location in a game should they become disconnected. We do not use cookies to collect personal information.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, just let us know. We limit email contact to information directly related to your purpose for registering at our site, such as providing you with login information, information about the products you have purchased, receipts, news about our site, and other information related directly to your activities on our site.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line we will only use it only for the purpose of delivering to you a product your requested. We do not distribute it to anyone else for any reason.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to unique identifier information (e.g., customer number or password) that we maintain about them, transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we maintain about them, contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them , and a description of information that we maintain about them.

Customers can access this information by contacting us.

With respect to security: We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. All information we collect from you is stored on secure servers, and never in hard copy.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Specifically, Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Google does this for any site you visit unless you tell them not to, this practice is not limited to our site, but we feel obligated to tell you that they do this. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact The DMA's Committee on Ethical Business Practices at [mgoldberger@the-dma.org](mailto:mgoldberger@the-dma.org), state or local chapters of the Better Business Bureau, state or local consumer protection office or just contact us and we will be happy to discuss it with you. We value your privacy and data security.
